export const MCQ = [
  {
    question: 'Which planet is the closest to Sun?',
    options: [
      { optionId: 'A', optionText: 'Venus' },
      { optionId: 'B', optionText: 'Mercury' },
      { optionId: 'C', optionText: 'Earth' },
      { optionId: 'D', optionText: 'Mars' },
    ],
    answer: 'B',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which data structure organizes items in First-In,First-Out (FIFO) manner?',
    options: [
      { optionId: 'A', optionText: 'Stack' },
      { optionId: 'B', optionText: 'Queue' },
      { optionId: 'C', optionText: 'Tree' },
      { optionId: 'D', optionText: 'Graph' },
    ],
    answer: 'B',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which of the following is primarly used for structuring web pages?',
    options: [
      { optionId: 'A', optionText: 'Python' },
      { optionId: 'B', optionText: 'Java' },
      { optionId: 'C', optionText: 'HTML' },
      { optionId: 'D', optionText: 'C++' },
    ],
    answer: 'C',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which planet is the closest to Sun?',
    options: [
      { optionId: 'A', optionText: 'Venus' },
      { optionId: 'B', optionText: 'Mercury' },
      { optionId: 'C', optionText: 'Earth' },
      { optionId: 'D', optionText: 'Mars' },
    ],
    answer: 'B',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which chemical symbol stands for Gold?',
    options: [
      { optionId: 'A', optionText: 'Au' },
      { optionId: 'B', optionText: 'Gd' },
      { optionId: 'C', optionText: 'Ag' },
      { optionId: 'D', optionText: 'Pt' },
    ],
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which of these process is not typically involved in refining petroleum?',
    options: [
      { optionId: 'A', optionText: 'Fractional Distillation' },
      { optionId: 'B', optionText: 'Cracking' },
      { optionId: 'C', optionText: 'Polymerizaton' },
      { optionId: 'D', optionText: 'Filtration' },
    ],
    answer: 'D',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the value of 12+28?',
    answer: '40',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the value of 12+28?',
    answer: '40',
  },
  {
    question: 'How many states are there in United States?',
    answer: '50',
  },
  {
    question: 'In which year was the Decleration of Independence signed?',
    answer: '1776',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the value of Pi rounded to the nearest integer?',
    answer: '3',
  },
  {
    question:
      'If a car travels at 50mph for 2 hours, how many miles does it travel?',
    answer: '120',
  },
];